Pete Welding collection, 1958-1995
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 8: Sound recordings
  - Subseries 1: Artists, bands, and interviews
    - Art Pepper Quartet - Art Pepper Quintet - Shorty Rogers and His Giants - Bud Shank-Shorty Rogers - Shelly Manne and His Men, 1952-1954, AFC 2011/053: SR528; RXH 5390; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 01:05:47, Side 2: 01:05:47): analog, 3 3/4 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Logger's note: Dubs from various commercial recordings: Art Pepper Quartet (Discovery 3019; 1953), Art Pepper Quintet (Discovery 3023; 1954), Modern Sounds - Shorty Rogers and His Giants (Capitol Records, H 294; 1952), Cool and Crazy - Shorty Rogers and His Giants (RCA Victor 3138; 1953), Compositions of Shorty Rogers - Bud Shank Quintet (NLP 2A; 1954), Shelly Manne and His Men, vol. 2 (Contemporary 2511, 1954)
      Start "Brown Gold" by the Art Pepper Quartet
      00:02:22 "Holiday Flight" by the Art Pepper Quartet
      00:05:28 "These Foolish Things" by the Art Pepper Quartet
      00:08:06 "Surf Ride" by the Art Pepper Quartet
      00:10:55 "Tickle Toe" by the Art Pepper Quartet
      00:13:45 "Everything Happens To Me" by the Art Pepper Quartet
      00:16:50 "Chili Pepper" by the Art Pepper Quartet
      00:19:43 "Susie The Poodle" by the Art Pepper Quartet
      00:22:54 "Straight Life" by the Art Pepper Quintet
      00:25:40 "Deep Purple" by the Art Pepper Quintet
      00:29:30 "What's New" by the Art Pepper Quintet
      00:32:52 "The Way You Look Tonight" by the Art Pepper Quintet
      00:36:31 "Cinnamon" by the Art Pepper Quintet
      00:39:38 "Nutmeg" by the Art Pepper Quintet
      00:42:45 "Thyme Time" by the Art Pepper Quintet
      00:46:09 "Art's Oregano" by the Art Pepper Quintet
      00:49:15 "Popo" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      00:52:13 "Over The Rainbow" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      00:55:07 "Four Mothers" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      00:57:48 "Didi" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      01:00:10 "Sam and the Lady" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      01:03:08 "Apropos" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      01:05:47 End
      Start "Coop De Graas" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      00:02:54 "Infinity Promenade" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      00:06:25 "Short Stop" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      00:09:38 "Boar-Jibu" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      00:13:12 "Contours" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      00:16:32 "Tale Of An African Lobster" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      00:19:55 "Chiquito Loco" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      00:23:19 "Sweetheart Of Sigmund Freud" by Shorty Rogers and His Giants
      00:25:55 "Casa De Luz" by Bud Shank Quintet
      00:31:23 "Lotus Bud" by Bud Shank Quintet
      00:34:41 "Left Bank" by Bud Shank Quintet
      00:37:58 "Shank's Pranks" by Bud Shank Quintet
      00:41:08 "Jasmine" by Bud Shank Quintet
      00:45:14 "Just A Few" by Bud Shank Quintet
      00:49:25 An unidentified piece by Shelly Manne and His Men
      00:51:41 "Etude De Concert" by Shelly Manne and His Men
      00:58:03 "Alternations" by Shelly Manne and His Men
      01:01:25 "Divertimento For Brass And Rhythm" by Shelly Manne and His Men
      01:04:18 "Dimension In Third" by Shelly Manne and His Men [cut off]
    - Oscar Pettiford - Orchestra, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR559; RXH 5420; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
    - Flip Phillips / Del Staton, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR743; RAA 59281; 1 sound tape reel (00:31:53): analog, 15 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Vendor's digitization note: The program has distortion, hiss, and hum from the source tape. The end of the recording cuts off abruptly.
    - Edith Piaf special, KPEK, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR682; RXH 5559; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
    - Piano album / Side D, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR547; RXH 5409; 1 sound tape reel (00:18:17): analog; 7 in.
      Includes works by Phineas Newborn, Bud Powell, Billy Taylor, and Tommy Flanagan.
      Start "How High the Moon" by Phineas Newborn
      00:03:08 "Round Midnight" by Phineas Newborn
      00:06:06 "Round Midnight" by Bud Powell
      00:13:13 "Indiana" by Billy Taylor
      00:15:15 "Anything I Do" by Tommy Flanagan
      00:18:17 End
    - Rod Piazza Band - "Live" at The Boiler Room, April 30, 1977, AFC 2011/053: SR173; RXH 4056; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester; Side 1: 00:21:00, Side 2: 00:21:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.
      Recorded at The Boiler Room, Claremont, California. Recorded and produced by Pete Welding. Rough mix from master tapes, for audition purposes. See SR174 and SR175. Collector's original ID number: 223.
      Logger's note: Rod Piazza sings and plays harmonica, George Phelps and Hollywood Fats play guitar, Larry Taylor plays bass and Dick Innes plays drums.
      Start Rod Piazza (RP) plays and sings "Rockin' Daddy"
      00:04:54 The second song by RP titled "Mean Old World"
      00:08:37 RP and the band perform "Take a Walk with Me"
      00:12:55 RP performs "My Babe"
      00:16:07 RP and the band play their last piece called "Third Degree"
      00:20:50 End
      Start An explanation of the amount of Hz [hertz] needed for operating the machine
      00:00:51 Rod Piazza (RP) plays and sings his first titled "Ooh Baby (Everything Gonna Be All Right)"
      00:05:13 RP performs his next piece called "Key to the Highway"
      00:09:09 RP performs "Mellow Down Easy"
      00:12:46 The next song by RP titled "Standing Around Crying"
      00:17:14 RP performs "Goin' Down Slow"
      00:20:57 End
    - Rod Piazza, George Phelps, Hollywood Fats, Larry Taylor, and Dick Innes, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR174; RXH 4057; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester; Side 1: 00:20:30, Side 2: 00:21:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.
      See the notes for SR173; see also SR175. Collector's original number: 224.
      Start Rod Piazza (RP) performs his first song with his band, the title is unknown
      00:04:33 The second selection by RP titled "Key to the Highway"
      00:08:31 PR performs "Mellow Down Easy"
      00:12:09 PR performs "Look How You Got Me Standing Around"
      00:16:40 The next selection by PR
      00:20:25 End
      Start Rod Piazza (RP) performs his first song with his band
      00:04:55 The second piece by RP, title unknown
      00:08:40 RP performs his next piece, "Take a Walk with Me"
      00:13:00 RP performs "My Babe"
      00:16:13 The final piece
      00:20:59 End
    - Rod Piazza Band - "Live" at The Boiler Room, reel #4, April 30, 1977, AFC 2011/053: SR175; RXH 4058; 1 sound tape reel (acetate master tape, 00:17:20): analog, 15 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      See SR173 and SR174.
      Start Rod Piazza (RP) performs his first song
      00:08:44 The second instrumental piece by RP, title is unknown
      00:12:52 RP introduces the band
      00:13:30 The last instrumental selection by RP
      00:17:20 End
    - Rod Piazza and The House Rockers, circa 1970s, AFC 2011/053: SR517; RXH 5379; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:21:25, Side 2: 00:20:21): analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Logger's note: Recorded live at The Boiler Room (club), Claremont, CA. Rod Piazza, vocal, harmonica.; George Phelps, Hollywood Eats, guitars; Larry Taylor, bass; Dick Innes, drums. Recorded and produced by Pete Welding (information from the tape box). Dub copy.
      00:00:35 "Rockin' Daddy"
      00:05:28 "Mean Old World"
      00:09:05 "Take a Little Walk with Me"
      00:13:26 "My Babe"
      00:16:40 "Third Degree"
      Start "Aw baby (You're Gonna Miss Me When I'm Gone)"
      00:04:25 "Key to the High Way"
      00:08:27 "Mellow Down Easy"
      00:12:05 "Standing Around Crying"
      00:16:36 "Going Down Slow"
      00:20:21 End
    - Rod Piazza (dub copy), undated, AFC 2011/053: SR523; RXH 5385; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:20:42, Side 2: 00:20:46): analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Vendor's digitization note: The program is distorted at times, and there is phasing. On Side 2, the right channel cuts in and out throughout program.
      00:00:22 Lyrics: Oh baby, you are gonna miss me when I am gone
      00:04:50 "Key to the Highway"
      00:08:48 "Mellow Down Easy"
      00:12:25 Lyrics: You are not nothing like you used to be...I am gonna ride you in my auto mobile...
      00:16:58 Lyrics: If I have my fun tonight, don't wait no more, I am going down soon...my baby doesn't care about me...
      Start Lyrics: Baby you are rocking all night long...I am going to rock you all night long...
      00:04:50 Lyrics: Sometimes I wonder why your love is so cold....
      00:08:32 "Take a Walk with Me"
      00:12:50 Lyrics: My baby doesn't say anything my baby...She is my baby....
      00:16:01 Lyrics: I can't stand no more...I can't even write my name...
      00:20:46 End
    - Rod Piazza Band - at the Boiler Room, Claremont, California - Transfer #1, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR798; RAA 59335; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips, 2 track, stereo; 10 in.
    - Rod Piazza Band - at the Boiler Room, Claremont, California - Transfer #2, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR799; RAA 59336; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips, 2 track, stereo; 10 in.
    - Rod Piazza Band - at the Boiler Room, Claremont, California - Transfer #3, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR800; RAA 59337; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips, 2 track, stereo; 10 in.
    - Rod Piazza Band - at the Boiler Room, Claremont, California - Transfer #4, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR801; RAA 59338; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips, 2 track, stereo; 10 in.
    - Rod Piazza #1 (set 1), April 30, 1977, AFC 2011/053: SR806; RAA 59343; 1 sound tape reel (Parts 1-4: 00:39:21 each; mix-down: 00:39:28): analog, 15 ips, four-track, mono; 10 in.
      Archivist's note: SR806, SR807, and SR808 were recorded live, probably in a Los Angeles music venue. Personnel: Rod Piazza: vocal and harmonica; George Phelps, guitar; Hollywood Fats, guitar; Larry Taylor, bass; Dick Innes, drums. The song titles follow, as much as possible, the titles as announced during the performance. See SR173, SR174, and SR175.
      This is a log of the mix-down.
      Start "Aw Baby, Gonna Miss Me When I'm Gone"
      00:06:06 "Key to the Highway"
      00:10:35 "Boom Boom - Out Go the Lights"
      00:15:07 "Third Degree"
      00:21:04 "Rockin' Daddy"
      00:25:58 "Mean Old World"
      00:29:49 "It Should've Been Me, Darlin'"
      00:33:28 "Tighten Up On Me Baby"
      00:38:43 Audio ends
      00:39:28 End
    - Rod Piazza #1 [sic] (sets 2 and 3), April 30, 1977, AFC 2011/053: SR807; RAA 59344; 1 sound tape reel (Parts 1-4: 00:40:28 each; mix-down: 00:40:32): analog, 15 ips, four-track, mono; 10 in.
      See the archivist's note for SR806. See also SR173, SR174, and SR175.
      Start "Too Late"
      00:06:44 "You're Looking Good Tonight"
      00:10:07 "You Better Watch Yourself"
      00:12:56 Unidentified instrumental blues song
      00:16:36 A brief glitch in the audio, where a very brief clip from a song performed by the same band can be heard
      00:16:38 "My Baby Don't Stand No Cheating" ["My Babe"]
      00:19:53 A second, brief glitch in the audio, where a very brief clip from another song performed by the same band can be heard
      00:19:58 "Mellow Down Easy"
      00:23:37 "Standing Around Crying"
      00:28:14 "I've Had My Fun"
      00:32:14 "Take A Little Walk With Me"
      00:37:41 Audio ends
      00:40:32 End
    - Rod Piazza #3 (sets 1 and 2), April 30, 1977, AFC 2011/053: SR808; RAA 59345; 1 sound tape reel (Parts 1-4: 00:38:14 each; mix-down: 00:37:20): analog, 15 ips, four-track, mono; 10 in.
      Start "Bad Actor" [?]--instrumental
      00:08:14 "Off the Wall" [?]--instrumental
      00:13:10 A brief snippet of a song, cut off
      00:13:16 "Help Me"
      00:18:13 "Early One Morning"
      00:22:36 "Mother-In-Law Blues"
      00:26:43 "Steady As A Bitch"
      00:31:12 "Five Long Years"
      00:36:37 Audio ends
      00:37:20 End
    - Rod Piazza, reel 2, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR812; RAA 59349; 1 sound tape reel (00:24:18): analog, 15 half track, stereo; 10 in.
      This may have been recorded at the same date and venue as SR806-SR808. See the archivist's note for SR806.
      Vendor's digitization note: The program is distorted at times, and there is high-frequency noise from the tape. A small amount of audio can be heard at the tail of the tape.
      00:04:31 "Key to the Highway"
      00:08:30 "Mellow Down Easy"
      00:12:09 "Standing Around Crying"
      00:16:41 "Going Down Slow"
      00:20:26 Gap in audio, until 00:20:34
      00:20:34 Unidentified blues tune
      00:24:18 End
    - Rod Piazza - dub - Side 1, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR741; RAA 59279; 1 sound tape reel (00:27:24): analog, 15 ips, half track mono, 2 track; 10 in.
      Vendor's digitization note: The Howlin' Wolf segment (towards the end of the program) is interrupted by several pauses in recording from 00:22:20-00:22:50, and speed ramps occur when recording resumes. The program has distortion and hiss from the source tape, as well as print-through. There is a long gap of silence during the program, and the end of the recording is cut off.
    - Rod Piazza 2 - dub - Side 1, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR742; RAA 59280; 1 sound tape reel (00:33:24): analog, 15 ips, half track, stereo; 10 in.
    - "Porkin' and Plowin'," circa mid-1970s, AFC 2011/053: SR329; RXH 4214; 1 sound tape reel (00:03:52): analog, 15 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Archivist's note: An unidentified rock band, with a male lead singer, and female singers on the chorus. The date is a guess. A song about sexual relations, with nothing left to the imagination.
    - Mel Powell - Mel Powell Trio - Ruby Braff-Ellis Larkins - Vic Dickenson Septet, circa 1953-1956, AFC 2011/053: SR526; RXH 5388; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Archivist's note: Recordings dubbed from various commercial releases. This recording has not yet been digitized. The list of recordings comes from the accompanying documentation and will need to be compared to the recordings.
      Start "Gone With The Wind" - Mel Powell (dubbed from the UK mono reissue of Out On A Limb, 1955; Vanguard VRS 8528)
      n/a "Bunny Hug" - Mel Powell (dubbed from the UK mono reissue of Out On A Limb, 1955; Vanguard VRS 8528)
      n/a "Pennies From Heaven" - Mel Powell (dubbed from the UK mono reissue of Out On A Limb, 1955; Vanguard VRS 8528)
      n/a "Stomping At The Savoy" - Mel Powell (dubbed from the UK mono reissue of Out On A Limb, 1955; Vanguard VRS 8528)
      n/a "When Your Lover Has Gone" - Mel Powell (dubbed from the UK mono reissue of Out On A Limb, 1955; Vanguard VRS 8528)
      n/a "Cooch" - Mel Powell (dubbed from the UK mono reissue of Out On A Limb, 1955; Vanguard VRS 8528)
      n/a "Beale St. Blues" - Mel Powell (dubbed from the UK mono reissue of Out On A Limb, 1955; Vanguard VRS 8528)
      n/a "Three Little Words" - Mel Powell (dubbed from the UK mono reissue of Out On A Limb, 1955; Vanguard VRS 8528)
      n/a "You're Lucky To Me" - Mel Powell (dubbed from the UK mono reissue of Out On A Limb, 1955; Vanguard VRS 8528)
      n/a "Liza" - Mel Powell (dubbed from the UK mono reissue of Out On A Limb, 1955; Vanguard VRS 8528)
      n/a "The Best Things In Life" - Mel Powell (dubbed from the UK mono reissue of Out On A Limb, 1955; Vanguard VRS 8528)
      n/a "Rosetta" - Mel Powell (dubbed from the UK mono reissue of Out On A Limb, 1955; Vanguard VRS 8528)
      n/a "Thigamagig" - Mel Powell Trio (dubbed from the US mono issue of Thigamagig, 1954; Vanguard VRS 8502)
      n/a "You're My Thrill" - Mel Powell Trio (dubbed from the US mono issue of Thigamagig, 1954; Vanguard VRS 8502)
      n/a "Button Up Your Overcoat" - Mel Powell Trio (dubbed from the US mono issue of Thigamagig, 1954; Vanguard VRS 8502)
      n/a "Don-Que-Dee" - Mel Powell Trio (dubbed from the US mono issue of Thigamagig, 1954; Vanguard VRS 8502)
      n/a "Bouquet" - Mel Powell Trio (dubbed from the US mono issue of Thigamagig, 1954; Vanguard VRS 8502)
      n/a "Ain't She Sweet" - Mel Powell Trio (dubbed from the US mono issue of Thigamagig, 1954; Vanguard VRS 8502)
      n/a "Take Me In Your Arms" - Mel Powell Trio (dubbed from the US mono issue of Thigamagig, 1954; Vanguard VRS 8502)
      n/a "California, Here I Come" - Mel Powell Trio (dubbed from the US mono issue of Thigamagig, 1954; Vanguard VRS 8502)
      n/a "My Funny Valentine" - Ruby Braff and Ellis Larkins (dubbed from the US issue of Two By Two: Ruby And Ellis Play Rodgers And Hart, 1956; Vanguard VRS 8507)
      n/a "In A Mountain Greenery" - Ruby Braff and Ellis Larkins (dubbed from the US issue of Two By Two: Ruby And Ellis Play Rodgers And Hart, 1956; Vanguard VRS 8507)
      n/a "Where Or When" - Ruby Braff and Ellis Larkins (dubbed from the US issue of Two By Two: Ruby And Ellis Play Rodgers And Hart, 1956; Vanguard VRS 8507)
      n/a "I Didn't Know What Time It Was" - Ruby Braff and Ellis Larkins (dubbed from the US issue of Two By Two: Ruby And Ellis Play Rodgers And Hart, 1956; Vanguard VRS 8507)
      Start "Blue Moon" - Ruby Braff and Ellis Larkins (dubbed from the US issue of Two By Two: Ruby And Ellis Play Rodgers And Hart, 1956; Vanguard VRS 8507)
      n/a "I Could Write A Book" - Ruby Braff and Ellis Larkins (dubbed from the US issue of Two By Two: Ruby And Ellis Play Rodgers And Hart, 1956; Vanguard VRS 8507)
      n/a "Thou Swell" - Ruby Braff and Ellis Larkins (dubbed from the US issue of Two By Two: Ruby And Ellis Play Rodgers And Hart, 1956; Vanguard VRS 8507)
      n/a "My Romance" - Ruby Braff and Ellis Larkins (dubbed from the US issue of Two By Two: Ruby And Ellis Play Rodgers And Hart, 1956; Vanguard VRS 8507)
      n/a "You Took Advantage Of Me" - Ruby Braff and Ellis Larkins (dubbed from the US issue of Two By Two: Ruby And Ellis Play Rodgers And Hart, 1956; Vanguard VRS 8507)
      n/a "Little Girl Blue" - Ruby Braff and Ellis Larkins (dubbed from the US issue of Two By Two: Ruby And Ellis Play Rodgers And Hart, 1956; Vanguard VRS 8507)
      n/a "I Married An Angel" - Ruby Braff and Ellis Larkins (dubbed from the US issue of Two By Two: Ruby And Ellis Play Rodgers And Hart, 1956; Vanguard VRS 8507)
      n/a "The Girl Friend" - Ruby Braff and Ellis Larkins (dubbed from the US issue of Two By Two: Ruby And Ellis Play Rodgers And Hart, 1956; Vanguard VRS 8507)
      n/a "Romance In The Dark" - Ruby Braff (dubbed from the US issue of The Ruby Braff Special, circa 1956; Vanguard VRS 8504)
      n/a "When You Wish Upon A Star" - Ruby Braff (dubbed from the US issue of The Ruby Braff Special, circa 1956; Vanguard VRS 8504)
      n/a "I Don't Stand A Ghost Of A Chance With You" - Ruby Braff (dubbed from the US issue of The Ruby Braff Special, circa 1956; Vanguard VRS 8504)
      n/a "Wishing (Will Make It So)" - Ruby Braff (dubbed from the US issue of The Ruby Braff Special, circa 1956; Vanguard VRS 8504)
      n/a "Where's Freddie" - Ruby Braff (dubbed from the US issue of The Ruby Braff Special, circa 1956; Vanguard VRS 8504)
      n/a "I'm In The Market For You" - Ruby Braff (dubbed from the US issue of The Ruby Braff Special, circa 1956; Vanguard VRS 8504)
      n/a "Sweet Sue (Just You)" - Ruby Braff (dubbed from the US issue of The Ruby Braff Special, circa 1956; Vanguard VRS 8504)
      n/a "Linger Awhile" - Ruby Braff (dubbed from the US issue of The Ruby Braff Special, circa 1956; Vanguard VRS 8504)
      n/a "Keeping Out Of Mischief Now" - Vic Dickenson Septet (dubbed from the US issue of Vic Dickenson Septet, vol. 2, 1953; Vanguard VRS 8002)
      n/a "Russian Lullaby" - Vic Dickenson Septet (dubbed from the US issue of Vic Dickenson Septet, vol. 1, 1953; Vanguard VRS 8001)
    - Doug Quattlebaum / Arts Council #4, February 6, 1961, AFC 2011/053: SR103; RXH 3652; on one side of 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:29:34): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Logger's note: This SR is in two parts. The first is three unidentified blues songs by Doug Quattlebaum. This is followed by Arts Council #4, an unidentified woman speaking about art, artists, and collecting art.
      Start unidentified blues already started. (perhaps "When My Baby Got On Board")
      00:02:40 unidentified blues. (perhaps "Do My Baby Think of Me")
      00:05:15 unidentified blues. (perhaps "Mean Old Frisco")
      00:07:35 An unidentified woman talks about art, artists and art collections.
      00:11:05 She talks about building an art collection.
      00:13:15 She invites questions and answers them. (For the most part, the questions are unintelligible.) She talks about buying and collecting art in sundry regions of the country.
      00:22:40 She is asked if she has a stable of artists and galleries for her collection. She responds.
      00:25:02 She is asked how many new artists she has taken on in the last year. She responds.
      00:29:43 End
    - Jimmy Raney - Eddie Harris - Ruby Braff, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR643; RXH 5520; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
    - Elis Regina / Trio Tamba / Joao Donato, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR565; RXH 5426; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
    - Renaissance - Tape Cantata, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR687; RXH 5564; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
    - Gordon Robertson / Robert Pete Williams, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR344; RXH 4229; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:48:02, Side 2: 00:45:31): analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 5 in.
      Collector's original ID number: 193.
      Archivist's note: Both tape sides include an interview interspersed with performances. Notes on the tape box indicate Robertson's recording is Side 1, and Williams's recording is Side 2. The notes also indicate Robertson is a Clarksdale street musician, although on the recording he says he is from St. Louis.
      Vendor's digitization note: The program is distorted at times, and there is high-frequency noise from the tape.
      Start "The Walkin' Blues"
      00:05:57 "Walk Up Blues" (song which resulted when asked how he made up the blues)
      00:10:50 "Rock Well Blues"
      00:16:10 Lyrics: "Bottle Up and [Oo] - (N*gg*r and white man playing [?] up n*gg*r [?] [?] up 'braid to [?] it up) strumming the guitar and talking which eventually led into a songLyrics: "
      00:25:42 Lyrics: "Goin' Away (on the [?] of my [?] goodly before leaving for Boston)"
      00:30:03 "What You Got On Your Mind?"
      00:32:37 "Up And Down Blues"
      00:38:48 "Ain't It Hard To Be A N*gg*r? ([?] Babe)"
      00:41:21 Conversing about songs including raggedy song per request of interviewer and playground game/ring play described as shift and show
      00:44:58 "Shippy Sloh (Ring Play)"
      00:46:51 Bit Of "Booker T. Washington" sung by [?] mother
      00:48:02 End
      Start Interviewer asks questions, says he's from St. Louis and he came to Jackson on bus. Interviewer requests a song about himself.
      00:01:01 "Pilgrim And A Stranger (Wayfaring Stranger)"
      00:03:37 "I'm Going Home to Tell My Jesus"/interviewer requests to pick in another style
      00:05:40 "If I Had My Way I'd Tear That Building Down"
      00:08:03 "I'm On My Way (Coming Home Some Day)"
      00:10:49 "Going Back to St. Louis (Going To Settle Down)"
      00:12:51 "Baby's Gone Blues"
      00:16:34 Short interview about his travels
      00:17:10 "Baby Left This Morning"
      00:19:51 interviewer requests song about singer
      00:22:22 interviewer asks how much money singer makes, singer's favorite spiritual
      00:23:55 Get On Board Little Children
      00:26:52 interviewer requests spiritual about Christmas: "Santa Clause if you don't bring me no [?] they don't bring my baby/Santa Clause if you bring me my baby I don't want no Christmas"
      00:29:10 interviewer requests song from a record
      00:32:45 [restarting song]
      00:36:39 End of recording of Gordon Roberston